GARY BURNER

Philadelphia, PA 19145 | (412) 518-2935 | grburner@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I recently graduated the University of Pennsylvania's Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp. After gaining unique experiences in multiple industries over the past 8 years I decided that web development and data analysis best fit my skillset and passion for always learning. The Penn LPS bootcamp provided me with a 6 month, deep dive into the MERN stack, with a focus on teamwork in a remote environment and creative problem solving.

Skills

- JavaScript
- React
- Express
- MongoDB

- SOL
- AWS
- ECommerce
- Data Collection and Analysis

Education

University of Pennsylvania

LPS Coding Bootcamp Certificate

May - Oct 2020

May 2012

Pennsylvania State University

Bachelor of Science: Finance

Work History

Wine Specialist & Department Lead

Feb 2018 - Current

Philadelphia, PA

- DiBruno Brothers Exceeded planned revenue by an average of 23% each month while managing all aspects of the department
 - Increased month over month revenue while navigating structural and operations changes due to COVID
 - Lead a small but effective team of 3 wine specialists

Publisher Manager - 50onRed & Tiller

Jan 2016 - Feb 2018

Red Spark

Philadelphia, PA

- Developed new and maintained existing publisher relationships, representing \$12MM (100% of total supply) on 50onRed's publisher platform
- Onboarded new publishers to generate a 9.41% revenue increase while managing 50onRed's publishers
- Improved communication between sales and technical teams for smoother implementations of new products and publisher onboarding
- Helped develop and launch a new product: Tiller. Responsible for onboarding new publishers, gathering product feedback and developing a product roadmap.

Co Owner, COO

Oct 2014 - Jan 2016

Philadelphia, PA

Food Underground

Jun 2012 - Feb 2015

Treasury Sales Analyst

PNC Bank Philadelphia, PA

- Expanded key product sales by analyzing existing customer data to better segment market needs
- Attained a comprehensive understanding of PNC's products and designed technical sales presentations to depict revenue and operational impacts
- Coordinated client centric sales strategies to assist in exceeding our region's goal of \$5MM in new revenue
- Developed data models to identify opportunities for new revenue